question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "hard",
     "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;The Sims&quot; series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Portal 2&quot;, Cave Johnson started out Aperture Science as a shower curtain company.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Undertale, having a &quot;Fun Value&quot; set to 56-57 will play the &quot;Wrong Number Song Call&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Man&#039;s Tree.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "All of these maps were in &quot;Tom Clancy&#039;s Rainbow Six Siege&quot; on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, Border, Consulate.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The video game &quot;Fuel&quot; has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The names of Roxas&#039;s Keyblades in Kingdom Hearts are &quot;Oathkeeper&quot; and &quot;Oblivion&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Minecraft&quot;, gold tools are faster than diamond tools.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
